-往中间投  这里  -好的
-Right down the middle. Right here. -Okay.
-接住  -漂亮
-There we go. -Nice!
-再来遍  -孩子们  注意了
-<i>Throw again.</i>- Kids, listen up.
特大新闻
Big news.
不要告诉我们你又怀了个孩子
Please tell us you're not having another baby.
没有  孩子够多了
No, we're not having another baby.
而且我可以担保
And I can assure you,
那种事情不会再发生了
we will not be making that announcement ever again.
谢谢  这儿的兄弟姐妹够多了
Yeah, this family is big enough.
嘿  老爸  你清楚这点了吗
Hey, you completely clear on that, dad?
你干嘛指我
Why you pointin' your finger at me?
造人工程可是需要团队合作的
Having babies is a team effort.
什么意思
What do you mean?
问得好
This should be good.
呃...
Uh...
告诉你吧  特大新闻就是
You know what? Getting back to that big announcement...
我们要来次全家度假
We're going on a family vacation!
这可是查莉的第一次啊
And it's our first one with Charlie.
还有本人
And Gabe.
瞎说什么  你都度过多少次假了
What are you talking about? You've been on lots of vacations.
是吗  拜访做过
Okay, visiting
臀部吸脂手术后的奶奶
grandma after she had the fat sucked out of her butt.
可不算是去度假
Is not a vacation.
好吧  这次的度假绝对货真价实
Okay, this time we are going on a real vacation.
我们要去山上的一处滑雪胜地
To a ski resort in the mountains.
噢  那还有一段关于咱家的有趣历史
Oh, and here's an interesting piece of family history...
我们管那地方叫幸福小山丘
The place is called mount bliss.
故事就发生在
And it happens to be...
你爸和我结婚时
... Where your dad and I got married.
那是相当的浪漫啊
It's very romantic.
亲爱的  你打断我了
Honey, you just interrupted me.
我只是想直入主题  鲍伯
I was just trying to get to the point, Bob.
你知道你的故事又臭又长
You know your stories go on forever.
浪漫的场景又上演了
And the romance continues.
知道吗  我们结婚的那个周末
You know, the weekend we got married,
我们根本没想过要这么做
We weren't even planning on doing it.
就是结婚
Getting married.
然后我们就遇到了牧师劳森
Then we met judge Lawson
他说我俩就是天生一对
and he said we were perfect for each other.
-然后我们就答应了  -结婚
-So we did it. -Got married.
为什么一直这么说
Why do you keep saying that?
你没和他说过吗
Haven't you had the talk with him yet?
我还没和PJ说过呢
I haven't had the talk with P.J. Yet.
不用管我
I'm good.
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
■
后期： Johnny-Z  追忆似水年华
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第二十四集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E24  Snow Show, Part 1
噢  这里太漂亮了
Oh, isn't it beautiful?
承载了许多美好的回忆
A lot of good memories here.
还会有更多呢
More to come.
别告诉我整周都要这样
It's gonna be like this the whole week, isn't it?
好了  你们去找个地先坐下  我们去登记入住
All right, why don't you kids have a seat while we check in?
嘿  PJ  我要去趟洗手间
Hey, P.J., I have to go to the bathroom.
-能陪我一起来吗  -你都多大了
-Can you come with me? -Aren't you a little old for that?
我把滑雪裤穿反了
I put my ski pants on backwards.
首次度假总是这么麻烦
First vacation's always the hardest.
哇
Whoa.
我从你身上感受到了强大的气场
I am getting a very powerful vibe from you.
噢抱歉  我刚在闷热的旅行车里坐了四个小时
Oh sorry. I've been sitting in a hot minivan for four hours.
噢  宝贝  不是这个  其实我是个巫师
Oh, sweetie, no. No no no. I mean I'm a psychic.
-真的  巫师  -没错
-Really? You're a psychic? -Yeah.
冒犯的说一下  您看起来和普通人无异
'cause, no offense, but you kind of look like a normal person.
你知道我刚才想说什么吗
Did you know I was gonna say that?
你知道我刚刚才想说什么吗
Did you know I was gonna say <i>that?</i>
那样是没用的
It doesn't work that way.
是的  我知道
And yes, I did.
想免费算算命吗
Would you like a free reading?
你来告诉我
You tell me.
那我就给你露两手
I'll give you one anyway.
把手给我
Give me your hands.
噢  这次旅行
Oh, this trip is going.
对于你来说意义非常
To be a very important one for you.
我看到了你带了两只左脚的靴子
I'm seeing you will have two left feet.
还有  怪了
And... that's odd.
现在我看见你房间里有只熊
Now I see there is a bear in your room.
现在我知道为什么你会在大厅里算命了
And now I see why you give free readings in the lobby.
最后
And finally,
我看见了你将会面对面的遇到
I see you will come face to face.
你人生中的真爱
With the love of your life.
噢  不了  谢谢
Oh whoa. Okay. No thanks.
我...我刚和一个叫斯宾塞的
I... I just got out of a relationship.
分手
With this guy named Spencer,
所以我还没准备好再去拾起另一段感情
So I'm not really looking to meet anybody.
准没准备好不由你说  真是可爱
You think it's up to you. That's cute.
呃  抱歉  我接下电话
Uh, excuse me. I have to take this.
哪有电话
Take what?
您好
Hello?
噢  真是大吃一惊  骗人的
Oh, what a surprise. Not really.
走吧  你不想滑雪了吗
Come on, don't you want to go snowboarding?
我正在滑  看好了
I'm doing it right now. Check this out.
我刚摔断了我的脖子
I just broke my neck.
强悍
Sweet.
那你这一整天都要干嘛啊
So what are you gonna do all day?
客房服务
Room service!
这就是我的回答
Does that answer your question?
您点的餐  先生
Your order, sir.
薯条  炸薯片  浇上冰激凌的洋葱圈
French fries, potato chips and onion rings a la mode.
史塔科威尔先生
Mr. Starkwell?
盖比
Gabe.
你俩会认识
You two know each other?
史塔科威尔先生是我的三年级老师
Mr. Starkwell was my third-grade teacher.
盖比是我放弃教育事业的元凶
Gabe is the reason I quit teaching.
他也正是我去暑期学校的原因
And he's the reason I went to summer school.
你去暑期学校的原因是你有一张...
You went to summer school because you've got a mouth on you...
抱歉先生
Sir.
嘿  记得我吗
Hey, remember me?
你三年级的时候我也教过你吗
Did I have you for third grade too?
是啊
Yeah.
我们一起度过了两年的美好时光唉
We had two great years together.
看来真是三十年东河  三十年西河啊
Well, looks like the foot's on the other shoe now, isn't it?
你是不是想说三十年河东  三十年河西
Don't you mean the shoe is on the other foot?
你整天纠正我的日子结束了  马文
Your days of correcting me are over, Marvin.
噢  这一定很有趣吧
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
什么  噢  惨了  我带来了两只左脚的靴子了
What? Oh no. I brought two left boots by mistake.
等等...两只左脚
Wait... two left feet.
-哼  真是怪异  -哪怪异了
-Huh, that's weird. -What's weird?
是这样的  今天我在大厅里遇见了个巫师
Well, I met this psychic in the lobby.
然后她说了一些疯狂的预言
And she made some crazy predictions.
而且好像其中一个真的发生了
But one of them just kind of came true.
我也曾遇见过一个巫师  非要给我算命
I went to a psychic once. She was dead on about me,
说我将来会大红大紫
Said I was gonna be famous.
但是没实现
But that hasn't come true.
目前为止
Yet.
但我这个巫师更疯狂
But mine was crazy.
她说我将遇到人生中的真爱
She said I'd come face to face with the love of my life.
其实  很可能发生的  泰迪
Well, it could happen, Teddy.
幸福小山丘可是个魔幻圣地
Mount bliss is a magical place.
是吗  别高兴的太早
Well, don't get too excited.
她还说这间房里会有只熊
She also said there would be a bear in my room.
噢  快逃命吧
Oh! Run for your lives!
好吧  太诡异了
Okay, that's just weird.
是吗  我觉着挺可爱的
Really? I thought it was kinda cute.
好吧  我们去换回来
All right, we'll go take it back.
哇
Wow.
这风景真是永远也看不够
I could look at that view forever.
好了  看够了
Okay, that's enough.
嗯
Hmm.
从没看见过有这条小道
Never seen this trail before.
太好了
Cool.
好了  耶
All right, yeah!
■
此路不通
啊
Ahhh!
这是天堂吗
Am I in heaven?
-你好  -嗨
-Hello. -Hi.
拜
Bye!
嘿  亲爱的  你猜怎么着
Hey. Hey honey? Guess what?
我们其实没结婚  你想与我共进午餐吗
We're not actually married. Would you like to grab some lunch?
你说什么
What did you just say?
你想和我共进午餐吗
You want to grab some lunch?
不是这句  再往上一句
No, before that.
噢  事实上我们的婚礼是无效的
Oh, it turns out our wedding ceremony wasn't actually valid.
墨西哥菜喜欢吗
You feel like mexican?
什么叫我们并没有结婚
What do you mean we're not actually married?
小点声  我刚才在打听关于劳森牧师的事情
Whoa whoa, I was asking around about judge Lawson.
然后前台的人告诉我
And the guy at the front desk tells me
劳森是个骗子
he was like some kind of con man.
很显然  他所有主持的婚礼是假的
Apparently he did fake marriages all the time.
但他说咱俩是天生一对
But he said we were perfect for each other.
很显然  这也是谎话的一部分
Apparently it was just part of his scam.
知道吗  我打听到这有火锅店的
You know, there's this great fondue place I read about.
能别再说吃的了吗
Would you stop talking about food?
这很严肃  我是说  咱俩真的没有结婚
This is serious. I mean, we're not really married?
这个  根据宇宙之说
Well, according to the universe,
我们确实结婚了  亲爱的
of course we are, honey.
但根据科罗拉多州法律  就不好说了
According to the state of Colorado, not so much.
-噢  嘿  巫师女士  -噢  嗨
-Oh hey, psychic lady! -Oh hi.
我找了一整天的真爱
So I've been looking around all day for the love of my life.
但我还没找到他  我想问问什么时候能找到
And I haven't found him yet. So when's that gonna happen?
哦天啊  我也不知道
Oh gosh, I don't know.
预言并不是什么精密科学
Psychic prediction is not an exact science.
哈  根本就不能算做科学
Ha! It's not a science at all.
好吧  那能稍微给我点信息吗
Right. Can I at least have a little more info?
比如他性不性感
Like is he hot or not?
也不是很重要了  但最好说“性感”
Not that it matters, but please say "hot."
我只能告诉你的就是  睁大你的双眼
All I can tell you is keep your eyes open.
好的  睁着呢
Okay. Well, they're open.
他们开始去看那一群
And they're starting to see that this is a bunch of...
嗨
Hi.
我叫泰迪
I'm Teddy.
我叫布兰登
I'm Brandon.
哇  我猜这真的成真了
Wow. So I guess it's true.
什么成真了
What's true?
那个  你  我是说  我们
Well, you... I mean, us.
我以为都是瞎说的
I mean, I didn't believe it,
然后我带来了两只左脚的靴子
but then I had two left boots,
其实也不能说是脚
Which aren't actually feet,
但当你需要什么东西去散步时
but they're where feet go in.
你的确可以把脚伸进去
When you need something to walk in.
所以从某种程度上来说  他们是脚
So in a sense, they're feet.
-说啥呢  -好了  好了
-What? -Okay okay,
我现在看起来可能有点疯狂
I probably sound a little bit crazy right now.
但当一个巫师告诉你
But you would too if a psychic told you
你的房间里有只熊
there was a bear in your room,
而且真的有  某种程度上  你也会发疯的
Which there was... sort of.
噢  记住是在我的房间里  不是你的
Oh, and in my room, not in your room.
我不知道你房间里有什么
I don't know anything about your room.
我要先走了
I'm gonna go now.
我不是疯子
I'm not crazy.
真的  我不是疯子
Seriously, I'm not crazy!
晚饭我想要龙虾温度计
For dinner I would like the lobster thermometer.
那叫热月龙虾
It's lobster thermidor.
关于纠正我这件事  我怎么跟你说的
What did I say about correcting me?
如果我再纠正你  你就...
That if I did it again, you were going to...
好了  别说我没警告过你
Well, I can't say I didn't warn you.
那就别傻站着了  赶紧给我弄龙虾去
Now chop chop and get me my lobster.
我知道这不关我事
I know this is none of my business,
但是你欠下了一大笔账单
But you're running up quite a bill here.
你这话什么意思
What do you mean?
别告诉我你不知道什么叫客房服务
You don't know what room service is, do you?
知道啊  我要什么  你就送来什么
Yeah. I want things and you bring them to me.
大哥  这是要收费的
For an additional charge.
什么  还要花钱
Wait, it costs money?
还不便宜呢
A lot of money.
想看看有多不便宜吗
Shall we see how much money?
来看看我最喜爱的频道
Let's go to my favorite channel,
账单频道
The bill channel.
我滴妈呀
Oh mama!
三百刀
$300?!
我哪有那么多钱啊
I don't have that kind of money.
看来你还点了泡菜
Looks like you're in quite a pickle...
提前通知你下  价值八元
which, by the way, are $8.
看来爸妈要关我一辈子的禁闭
Mom and dad are gonna ground me forever.
也许我们可以化险为夷
Perhaps we can make some kind of arrangement.
什么意思
What do you mean?
当个行李员
I have to be a bellman?
行李童
Bellboy.
可可还很不错吧
How's the cocoa?
暖和了吗
Are you warming up?
这是天堂吗
Am I in heaven?
他怎么老说这句话
Why does he keep saying that?
我也不知道  不过挺可爱的
I don't know. But it's so cute.
这就是你们的小屋  是吧
So this is your cabin, huh?
是的
Yep.
我们这里不经常来访客的
We don't get a lot of visitors.
特别是有着一双闪闪发光的蓝眼睛
Especially ones with sparkling blue eyes.
还有漂亮的金发
And beautiful blonde hair.
看来今天大家的运气都不错
This is a lucky day for everyone.
你需要往家里打个电话
Do you need to call your family
告诉他们你没事吗
and let them know you're okay?
不用  现在挺好的
Nah, I'm good.
这么说来  只有你俩住在这里
So you girls live here alone?
-不是的  我们的爸爸和我们住在一起  -噢
-No, our pa lives with us. -Oh.
-但是他现在出差了  -噢
-But he's away on business. -Oh.
说说你为什么“误入歧途”了
Why did you go down the wrong side of the mountain?
因为...
Because...
-你们这里有电视吗  -没有
-Do you girls get T.V. Here? -No.
因为我要卫冕奥运会金牌  所以在这里训练
I'm training to defend my olympic gold medal.
哇
Wow.
太了不起了
That's amazing.
小可怜  你都冻坏了
You poor baby, you're freezing.
我去给你烧热洗澡水
I want to run him a hot bath.
-我去  -不  我去
-I will. -No, I will.
噢  美女们  一次可不够我洗的
Oh girls, girls. I'm gonna need more than one bath.
嘿  老妈  能借下你的粉围巾吗
Hey, mom, can I borrow your pink scarf?
可以  宝贝  你怎么弄得花枝招展的
Sure, honey. Why are you all dolled up?
因为我想我很可能遇见我的真爱了
Because I think I may have met the love of my life.
除了我在那疯颠颠的  然后把他吓跑
Except I acted crazy and scared him away,
所以现在我要变成万人迷  然后在大厅里转悠
So now I have to get super cute and hang out in the lobby.
最后让他投入我的怀抱
So he can fall in love with me.
妈  告诉你吧  他真是太完美了
Mom, I've got to tell you, he is the perfect guy.
是吗  好吧  和我多聊聊他
Well, okay, tell me all about him.
好的  首先他可爱之极
Okay. Well, he's really cute.
其次他叫布兰登
His name is Brandon.
再次  我就知道这么多了
And that's all I know.
他听起来是挺完美的
He does sound perfect.
嘿  亲爱的  嘿
Hey, honey. Hey.
你怎么还没准备好  我们不是要去滑雪吗
Why aren't you dressed? I thought we were going skiing.
不去了  情况有变
No, change of plans.
前台找到了一位治安法官
The front desk found a justice of the peace.
今天下午他要为我们主持婚礼
Who's going to marry us this afternoon.
你们说什么呢
What are you talking about?
呃  宝贝  你一定要淡定
Um, honey. I want you to brace yourself.
好吗  你爸和我其实没结婚
Okay? Your father and I aren't actually married.
天啊
Oh my gosh.
我居然忘了用牙线了
I forgot to floss.
-那我们去结婚吧  -好的
-So should we go get married? -Yeah.
但能先到家再结吗
But can't it wait till we get home?
那个  我本以为婚礼应该是浪漫且特殊的
Well, I just thought it would be really romantic and special.
而且在这里
If we did it here...
知道吗  十九年前我们曾假结婚的地方
You know, where we thought we did it 19 years ago.
但我都买好缆车票了
But I already bought the lift tickets.
噢  别这样啊  亲爱的  我们在度假
Oh, come on, honey! We're on vacation.
走吧  我想好好开心下
Come on, I want to enjoy myself.
哦好吧  那么和我结婚
Oh okay. So being married to me.
就不开心吗
Isn't something you'd enjoy?
此时此刻的确不怎么开心
I'm not enjoying it right now.
好吧  这婚不结了
Fine, don't marry me then.
什么  好吧  不结就不结
Well, all right, fine. I won't.
没有我你活不过五分钟
You won't last five minutes without me.
哦是吗  等着瞧好吧
Oh yeah? You just watch me.
-你看见我的那个...  -脖子上围着呢
-Have you seen that... -It's around your neck.
谢了
Thank you.
从现在开始计时  宝贝
Starting right now, baby!
多和我们讲讲你金牌的事情
Tell us more about your gold medal.
好的  首先它是金色的
Well, it's gold.
其次它由金属制成
And it's made out of metal.
我们还能为你做些什么呢
Can we get you anything else?
好的  那就弄点棉花糖来
Yeah. Why don't you get some marshmallows,
还有巧克力和全麦饼干
Some chocolate and some Graham crackers?
-做什么  -这样我们就可以做烧烤棉花糖了
-What for? -So we can make s'mores.
什么东西
What are those?
美女们啊
Girls, girls, girls,
你们要学的东西还真不少
There's so much I have to teach you.
-我来拿  -不  我来拿
-I'll get them. -No, I'll get them.
-我来拿  -啊
-I'll get them! -Ah!
哇  你哪位
Whoa! Who are you?
你哪位
Who are you?
我先问的
I asked you first.
我可不喜欢我的闺女们成天被男孩围着
I don't like boys sniffing around my girls.
你一定就是爸爸了
You must be pa.
哇
Wow.
您还真是硕大无比
You're bigger than everything.
滚出去
Get out.
我正有此意
My thoughts exactly.
那是我的长袍吗
Is that my robe?
好像是吧
Oh whoopsie.
给您
Here you go.
见到您很高兴  先生
Nice to meet you, sir.
我为您准备了烧烤棉花糖
Enjoy your s'mores.
拜
Bye.
好了  如果你娘我成单身了
Yeah, if mommy's gonna be single,
你也别想成双成对
You're gonna be single too.
嘿  宝贝  还在寻找你的真爱吗
Hey, honey, still looking for the love of your life?
是啊  就是找不到他啊
Yeah, and I can't find him anywhere.
妈  如果我只有那一次机会
Mom, what if I only had one chance
而且我还搞砸了呢
and I blew it?
我也有这种担心
I've been feeling exactly the same way.
什么
What?
因为你爸和我并没有结婚
Because dad and I aren't actually married.
现在他又不想娶我了
And he didn't want to marry me again.
我装出了一副满不在乎的样子
I know I'm putting up a brave front,
但其实我是真的受伤了
But I'm really hurting.
噢  没准就是他
Oh, maybe that's him!
嘿  老兄  还好吧
Hey, what's up? How's it going?
听着  如果有一个看起来很吓人
Listen, if a big scary guy
而且还有络腮胡子的人来找我
with a beard shows up,
就说我不在
I'm not here.
-客房服务  -好的  请进
-<i>Room service.</i> -Yeah, come on in.
亲爱的  点的餐来了
Honey, food's here.
-哇  -怎么了
-Wow. -What?
这么小就来工作了
Aren't you a little young to be working?
我遇到经济危机了
I got myself into some trouble.
你知不知道客房服务是收费的
Did you know that room service is extra?
-地球人都知道  -不一定啊  老兄
-Everyone knows that. -Not everyone, my friend.
很好很好  你能把它放在那里吗
Great great. Do you mind setting it up over there?
如果你能把沙拉拌好了  那就更好了
And if you could toss the salad, that would be great.
我老婆一会就出来了  好吗
My wife will be right out, okay?
好吧
Uh, sure.
呃
Ech!
-你在干什么  -拌沙拉啊
-What did you do? -I tossed the salad.
不  你在搞破坏  快出去
No, you've made a mess. Get out of here.
我还要打开苹果酒
I have to open the cider.
哎呦  我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
我去给你拿毛巾  别动
I'm gonna go get you a washcloth, okay?
如果还需要什么  记着叫我  我叫马文
If you need anything else, my name is Marvin.
我向您保证  先生
I assure you, sir,
等我们查出此人  必将严肃处理
when we find this person, they'll be dealt with severely.
冒出行李员是不可饶恕的
Impersonating a bellman is a serious offense.
好了  该去滑雪了
Well, time to go skiing.
-哇  -嗨
-Whoa. -Hi.
我...能撞上你还真是巧合哈
I... it's so weird running into you.
我可没一直找你
I haven't been looking for you.
好了  我能看见你眼神里的恐惧感
Okay, I see you have that scared look in your eye.
而且你很可能随时跑掉
And you're probably gonna bolt any second,
但在那之前
So before you do that,
我们能重新来过吗
Can we just start over?
好啊
Sure.
嘿  不如我去帮咱俩拿点热可可
Hey, why don't I grab us some hot cocoa.
你去帮忙找俩个位子
And you find us somewhere to sit?
透露下...壁炉旁边的就不错
P.S.... I look really great next to fires.
-那我们就在这里  -好的  我马上回来
-Then I'll be right here. -Well, I'll be right back.
-哇  -嗨
-Whoa. -Hi.
嗨
Hi.
我叫贾斯汀
I'm Justin.
噢  不  我们刚才面对面了
Oh no, we're face to face.
是啊  没错
Yeah. Yeah, we are.
但我已经面对面过了
But I already was face to face.
我可不能面对面再对面了
I can't be face to face to face.
等下  你说什么
Wait, what?
好吧  本来我以为是他
Well, you were supposed to be him,
但现在我觉着又是你
but now I guess it could be you.
算了  我去找巫师了
You know what? I need to talk to my psychic.
我马上回来  抱歉
I'll be right back. Sorry.
泰迪
Teddy.
斯宾塞
Spencer.
未完待续
下集预告
<i>Next time on</i> <i>"Good luck Charlie"...</i>
我们去哪凑那五百块钱
Where are we going to find $500?
这是您的最后机会来登记参加
This is your last chance to sign up.
冰上之舞比赛
For the ice-dancing contest.
获胜奖金...五百元
Grand prize... $500.
撑死我们也就能拿个第二名
We'll be lucky to finish second.
-那是因为只有两支队伍  -那你就配合我
-There are only two teams. -So you're following me.
啊
Ah!
为什么我需要一个新房间
Why do I have a new room?
因为我们还没正式结婚
Because you and I are not legally married.
除非你心甘情愿的
And since it would apparently inconvenience you
再次娶我为妻
to marry me again,
否则你将一直流离失所
You'll be lodging elsewhere.
她说在这次旅行中
She said I'd come face to face
我将面对面的遇到我的真爱
with the love of my life on this trip.
然而目前为止  我遇到了布兰登
And so far I've met Brandon,
贾斯汀  还有斯宾塞
Justin and... Spencer.
有些事情我一定要和你面对面的说
There's something I really need to tell you face to face.
别  别提面对面
No, don't say face to face.